[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The movie Superbad centers around two high school students trying to get laid before going to college.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor plays the evil Mac in the 2000 movie Romeo Must Die?", "correct_answer": "Isaiah Washington", "incorrect_answers": ["Edoardo Ballerini", "Delroy Lindo", "Anthony Anderson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the henchmen and secret police of the White Witch in the Chronicles of Narnia: The Lion, the Witch, and the Wardrobe?", "correct_answer": "Wolves", "incorrect_answers": ["Dwarfs", "Minotaurs", "Gnomes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which was the first implemented high-level general purpose programming language?", "correct_answer": "Fortran", "incorrect_answers": ["Cobol", "BASIC", "Pascal"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Woody Allen wrote and directed the 1978 drama Interiors in the manner of this European director, who was one of Allens major influences.", "correct_answer": "Ingmar Bergman", "incorrect_answers": ["Sergio Leone", "Michelangelo Antonioni", "Wim Wenders"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The red kangaroo appears on the Coat of Arms of Australia together with what other endemic Australian animal?", "correct_answer": "Emu", "incorrect_answers": ["Platypus", "Dingo", "Koala"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Pearls come in many shapes and sizes. What term refers to pearls with irregular shapes?", "correct_answer": "Baroque pearls", "incorrect_answers": ["Eggplant pearls", "All of these", "Semi-pearls"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Dead Presidents, Cutty was Kirbys nephew.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On average, only one baby in 10,000,000 is born with a tooth.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A turtles skin is made of scales, just like the skin of other reptiles.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Lacoste offers clothing for kids, men and women.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The mathematical constant Pi is inherently involved in which of these math problems ?", "correct_answer": "Squaring the circle", "incorrect_answers": ["Calculating the area of polygons", "Calculating the number of years it takes to double your money in an investment", "Finding the optimum value for the weight of a buildings foundation"]}]